<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Masquerade</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Masquerade</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Policy |</title>
      <link>/cookie-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cookie-policy/</guid>
      <description>Cookie Policy What is a Cookie? A Cookie is a piece of information, like a tag, that’s stored on your computer, tablet or phone when you visit our website. It can help identify the device you use whenever you visit us, so we can remember who you are. Cookies are used by websites, including ours, to provide you with a better experience when you visit and for other reasons, including remembering your preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Slavery &amp; Human Trafficking Statement |</title>
      <link>/modern-slavery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-slavery/</guid>
      <description>Modern Slavery &amp;amp; Human Trafficking Statement This statement is made on behalf of Baked Creative Limited pursuant to section 54 (1) of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 (the “Act”) and constitutes our slavery and human trafficking statement.
This statement sets out Baked’s actions to understand all potential modern slavery risks related to its business and to put in place steps that are aimed at ensuring that there is no slavery or human trafficking in its own business and its supply chains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy |</title>
      <link>/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Who we are Baked Creative Limited (we, us, our) is a company registered in England and Wales under company number 12099792 and our registered office address is C/O Smooth Accounting Limited, Building 1000 Lakeside North Harbour, Western Road, Portsmouth, United Kingdom, PO6 3EN.
You can get in touch with our data protection officer by writing to The Data Protection Officer at our address above or email hello@bakedcreative.co.
Managing your personal information This privacy policy sets out how we collect, use, and protect any information you give us when you use our website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
